https://www.detailking.com/using-our-site/privacy-policy/

INTERNATIONAL CUSTOMERS, Click here
Have a question? Visit our Contact page or call (724) 325-0008 | (724) 325-0066
Store Home
Clearance Items!
Sample Auto Detailing Business Plans
Detail King Authorized Licensee World Directoryof Car Detailing Professionals
About Auto Detailing Training
Auto Detailing Training Seminar – 3 Day Craftsman Class – Pittsburgh
Follow US
Find it Fast!
Search by keywords, sku/product ids,description
Store Home
Clearance Items!
Sample Auto Detailing Business Plans
Detail King Authorized Licensee World Directoryof Car Detailing Professionals
About Auto Detailing Training
Auto Detailing Training Seminar – 3 Day Craftsman Class – Pittsburgh
Using Our Site
Request a CatalogSign Up To Receive Our Newsletters & Secret Specials!Community & Commenting GuidelinesDetail King LP Return PolicyDetail King LP Refund PolicyPrivacy PolicySitemapTerms & Conditions2019 Detail King Catalog Download
Testimonials
My son Kyle and I attended the Craftsman Training from 02/21/20 to 02/23/20. Kyle’s desire for entrepreneurship and Cars is the driving force that brought us to Detail King. Folks we were not disappointed! Detail King training is just Outstanding. Nick Vacco and his staff at Detail King are World Class Professionals. I have no doubt if we follow the road map put before us by Detail King that success will come one detail job at a time.
This Dad gets the great bonus of watching his son achieve his dreams. I highly recommend Detail King to you entrepreneurs out there looking to start your own  Detailing Business and I totally recommend it to all working in the industry already who want to hone there skills. We expect to attend additional training in the future. To Nick and your Staff Thank You so much. You do change lives.
Michael Gilligan – Detail King are World Class Professionals
Take a moment to grab your copy of the 2019 Detail King Auto Detailing Products and Supplies catalog. It’s fully packed with our best products to help you make an informed purchasing decision.
Get the Detail King Newsletter!
Click here to receive helpful tips & tricks along with special offers by email.
Privacy Policy
Our Privacy Statement
We are highly sensitive to the privacy interests of consumers and believes that the protection of those interests is one of its most significant responsibilities. In acknowledgment of its obligations, we have adopted the following Privacy Policy applicable to information about consumers that it acquires in the course of its business:
1. Acquisition of Information. We do not acquire any more information about consumers than is required by law or is otherwise necessary to provide a high level of service efficiently and securely.
2. Our Employees and Privacy. We train all of our employees about the importance of privacy. We give access to information about consumers only to those employees who require it to perform their jobs.
3. Security Measures. We make access to privacy-sensitive information subject to rigorous procedural and technological controls, consistent with legal requirements and the demands of customer service.
4. Disclosure to Third Parties. We will provide individually-identifiable information about consumers to third parties only if we are compelled to do so by order of a duly-empowered governmental authority, we have the express permission of the consumer, or it is necessary to process transactions and provide our services.
5. Privacy and Our Business Partners. When we make our technology or services available to business partners, we will not share with them any more consumer information than is necessary, and we will make every reasonable effort to assure, by contract or otherwise, that they use our technology and services in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy.
Questions. If you have questions about this privacy policy, please contact us via email. Thank you.
© 1999 - 2020, Detail King®. All rights reserved. Website design by riggs creative.
